<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<transcript id="3041064" product="CorrectedTranscript" xmlns="http://www.factset.com/callstreet/xmllayout/v0.1">
  <meta>
    <title>Q2 2025 Earnings Call</title>
    <date>2025-07-15</date>
    <companies>
      <company>286</company>
    </companies>
    <participants>
      <!-- Operator -->
      <participant id="0" type="operator">Operator</participant>
      
      <!-- Corporate Representatives -->
      <participant id="1" type="corprep" affiliation="JPMorganChase" affiliation_entity="0035K2-E" entity="05K2VB-E">Jamie Dimon</participant>
      <participant id="2" type="corprep" affiliation="JPMorganChase" affiliation_entity="0035K2-E" entity="0CX9YZ-E">Jeremy Barnum</participant>
      
      <!-- Analysts -->
      <participant id="3" type="analyst" affiliation="Keefe, Bruyette &amp; Woods, Inc." affiliation_entity="000C7F-E" entity="0DZ2KL-E">Christopher McGratty</participant>
      <participant id="4" type="analyst" affiliation="Morgan Stanley &amp; Co. LLC" affiliation_entity="000BPH-E" entity="04KXN8-E">Betsy Graseck</participant>
      <participant id="5" type="analyst" affiliation="TD Cowen" affiliation_entity="000GRT-E" entity="05YHV3-E">Jared Shaw</participant>
      <participant id="6" type="analyst" affiliation="Bank of America Merrill Lynch" affiliation_entity="000C7F-E" entity="0H3K4M-E">Ebrahim Poonawala</participant>
      <participant id="7" type="analyst" affiliation="Truist Securities, Inc." affiliation_entity="000D9C-E" entity="06N9T-E">Brandon King</participant>
      <participant id="8" type="analyst" affiliation="Wells Fargo Securities LLC" affiliation_entity="000EPB-E" entity="0G2L9K-E">Mike Mayo</participant>
      <participant id="9" type="analyst" affiliation="UBS Securities LLC" affiliation_entity="000C7P-E" entity="0F4H8N-E">Erika Najarian</participant>
      <participant id="10" type="analyst" affiliation="Seaport Global Securities LLC" affiliation_entity="000J8K-E" entity="0K5M2P-E">Jim Mitchell</participant>
      <participant id="11" type="analyst" affiliation="Autonomous Research" affiliation_entity="000H5T-E" entity="0L6N3Q-E">John McDonald</participant>
      <participant id="12" type="analyst" affiliation="Deutsche Bank Securities, Inc." affiliation_entity="000BKL-E" entity="0M7P4R-E">Matt O'Connor</participant>
      <participant id="13" type="analyst" affiliation="Evercore ISI" affiliation_entity="000FGH-E" entity="0N8Q5S-E">Glenn Schorr</participant>
      <participant id="14" type="analyst" affiliation="RBC Capital Markets LLC" affiliation_entity="000DRT-E" entity="0P9R6T-E">Gerard Cassidy</participant>
      <participant id="15" type="analyst" affiliation="HSBC Securities (USA) Inc." affiliation_entity="000FKJ-E" entity="0Q1S7U-E">Saul Martinez</participant>
      <participant id="16" type="analyst" affiliation="Oppenheimer &amp; Co., Inc." affiliation_entity="000GHY-E" entity="0R2T8V-E">Chris Kotowski</participant>
    </participants>
  </meta>
  
  <body>
    <!-- Management Discussion Section -->
    <section name="MANAGEMENT DISCUSSION SECTION">
      <!-- Operator Introduction -->
      <speaker id="0">
        <plist>
          <p>Good morning, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to JPMorganChase's Second Quarter 2025 Earnings Call. This call is being recorded.</p>
          <p>At this time, I would like to turn the call over to JPMorganChase's Chairman and CEO, Jamie Dimon. Mr. Dimon, please go ahead.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <!-- CEO Opening Remarks -->
      <speaker id="1">
        <plist>
          <p>Thank you very much; and good morning, everyone. This quarter, the Firm reported net income of $18.1 billion, earnings per share of $6.12, and a return on tangible common equity of 21%. These are very strong results as our lines of business continued to perform well in what remains a relatively favorable environment.</p>
          <p>The U.S. economy continues to be resilient, with consumers still spending, albeit at a slower pace. Their balance sheets remain generally healthy, but we are seeing an increase in delinquencies particularly in certain cohorts.</p>
          <p>Looking at our business segments, we saw strong performance across the board. In Consumer &amp; Community Banking, we generated net income of $5.2 billion with deposits up 6% year-over-year. Our credit card sales volume was up 10%, and we added 2 million new card accounts this quarter.</p>
          <p>In the Corporate &amp; Investment Bank, we generated net income of $4.9 billion. Markets revenue was up 25%, with strong performance in both Fixed Income and Equities. Investment Banking fees were up 15%, with particular strength in M&amp;A advisory.</p>
          <p>Our Asset &amp; Wealth Management business generated net income of $1.1 billion, with client assets reaching a record $4.3 trillion.</p>
          <p>While we are pleased with our strong quarter, we remain vigilant about potential risks. Geopolitical tensions remain elevated, and we continue to closely monitor inflation, quantitative tightening, and fiscal deficits.</p>
          <p>Now let me hand it over to Jeremy to take you through the results in more detail.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <!-- CFO Detailed Review -->
      <speaker id="2">
        <plist>
          <p>Thanks, Jamie, and good morning, everyone. Starting with the financial results on page 2 of the earnings presentation.</p>
          <p>The Firm reported net income of $18.1 billion, or $6.12 per share, with a return on tangible common equity of 21%. These results include $7.9 billion after-tax, or $2.67 per share, of net investment securities gains.</p>
          <p>Net interest income ex. Markets was $22.9 billion, down 3%, as the impact of lower deposit margins was partially offset by higher card balances.</p>
          <p>Noninterest revenue ex. Markets was $8.4 billion, up 44%. Excluding the net gain on the sale of Visa shares of $7.9 billion after-tax, NIR ex. Markets was up 2%, driven by higher investment banking fees, partially offset by lower deposit-related fees in CCB.</p>
          <p>Markets revenue of $8.4 billion was up 25%. Fixed Income Markets was $4.5 billion, up 20%, and Equity Markets was $3.9 billion, up 32%.</p>
          <p>Expenses of $20.7 billion were up 11%, driven by higher compensation expense, including revenue-related compensation in the CIB and growth in headcount, as well as continued investments in technology.</p>
          <p>Credit costs of $3.1 billion included net charge-offs of $2.3 billion and a net reserve build of $789 million. The net reserve build was $2.9 billion in Card, reflecting loan growth and updates to certain macroeconomic variables, while there was a release of approximately $2.1 billion, which was split between Wholesale and other consumer portfolios.</p>
          <p>Moving to capital on page 3. Our CET1 ratio ended at 15.0%, up from 14.3% in the prior quarter, and approximately 60 basis points above the new 14.4% requirement that we disclosed last quarter. This increase reflects the benefit of net income and the Visa gain, partially offset by capital distributions.</p>
          <p>We distributed $4.5 billion of capital to shareholders this quarter, including $1.2 billion of common share dividends and $3.3 billion of share buybacks.</p>
          <p>Now let me go through each of the businesses in more detail, starting with Consumer &amp; Community Banking on page 4.</p>
          <p>CCB reported net income of $5.2 billion, including approximately $1.6 billion of the Visa gain. Revenue of $17.4 billion was up 4%, driven by higher net interest income in Card.</p>
          <p>In Banking &amp; Wealth Management, deposits were up 6% year-over-year and down 1% quarter-over-quarter. We continue to see migration to higher-yielding products, although at a moderating pace.</p>
          <p>Client investment assets were up 23% year-over-year to $894 billion, driven by market appreciation and net inflows.</p>
          <p>In Card Services, credit card spend was up 10% year-over-year, with travel and entertainment spend up 13%. We saw continued strong account acquisition with 2 million new accounts opened this quarter.</p>
          <p>Card loans were up 13% year-over-year. The net charge-off rate was 3.05%, compared to 2.63% in the prior year.</p>
          <p>Now turning to the Corporate &amp; Investment Bank on page 5. The CIB reported net income of $4.9 billion, including approximately $1.9 billion of the Visa gain.</p>
          <p>Investment Banking revenue of $2.4 billion was up 15%. We maintained our #1 rank with a wallet share of 9.0%. Advisory fees were up 25%, Equity underwriting was up 15%, and Debt underwriting was up 5%.</p>
          <p>Markets revenue of $8.4 billion was up 25%. Fixed Income Markets of $4.5 billion was up 20%, reflecting strength across products, particularly in rates and spread products. Equity Markets of $3.9 billion was up 32%, driven by strong client activity in derivatives and prime finance.</p>
          <p>Payments revenue of $2.7 billion was down 5%, as the impact of deposit margin compression more than offset higher fees and deposit growth.</p>
          <p>Securities Services revenue of $1.1 billion was flat, as higher fees on higher market levels were offset by deposit margin compression.</p>
          <p>Expenses of $7.5 billion were up 15%, predominantly driven by higher revenue-related compensation.</p>
          <p>Moving to Commercial Banking on page 6. Commercial Banking reported net income of $1.5 billion, including approximately $746 million of the Visa gain.</p>
          <p>Revenue of $3.8 billion was up 1%. Net interest income of $2.4 billion was down 10%, driven by lower deposit margins. Noninterest revenue of $1.4 billion was up 31%, or down 7% excluding the Visa gain, driven by lower lending-related fees.</p>
          <p>Expenses of $1.3 billion were up 6%, driven by continued investments in the business including technology and bankers.</p>
          <p>Average deposits of $262 billion were down 2% year-over-year and up 1% quarter-over-quarter.</p>
          <p>Loans were down 2% year-over-year and flat quarter-over-quarter at $238 billion. C&amp;I loans were down 1% and CRE loans were down 3%.</p>
          <p>Credit costs of $175 million included net charge-offs of $58 million.</p>
          <p>Finally, Asset &amp; Wealth Management on page 7. Asset &amp; Wealth Management reported net income of $1.1 billion, including approximately $526 million of the Visa gain.</p>
          <p>Revenue of $4.5 billion was up 18%. Net interest income of $1.9 billion was down 6%, driven by deposit margin compression. Noninterest revenue of $2.6 billion was up 47%, or up 2% excluding the Visa gain, driven by higher management fees on higher market levels, largely offset by deposit margin compression in our investment products.</p>
          <p>Expenses of $3.2 billion were up 6%, driven by higher compensation expense and continued investments in the business.</p>
          <p>AUM of $3.5 trillion was up 15% year-over-year, reflecting market appreciation and net inflows of $194 billion over the last twelve months.</p>
          <p>Overall client assets of $4.3 trillion, a new record, were up 18% year-over-year.</p>
          <p>And with that, we'll open the line for Q&amp;A.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <!-- Operator Transition to Q&A -->
      <speaker id="0">
        <plist>
          <p>Thank you. We will now begin the question and answer session. As a reminder, please limit yourself to one question and one follow-up.</p>
          <p>Our first question will come from Christopher McGratty with KBW. Your line is open.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
    </section>
    
    <!-- Q&A Section -->
    <section name="Q&amp;A">
      <!-- Question 1 -->
      <speaker id="3" type="q">
        <plist>
          <p>Great. Good morning. Thanks for the question. Jamie, relative to three months ago, there's a lot of optimism about the economy and the markets. Can you talk about how you're thinking about the outlook today, particularly given some of the recent economic data points? And any update on your views on interest rates would be helpful.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="1" type="a">
        <plist>
          <p>Yeah, look, I think the economy remains resilient. Consumer spending is still positive, employment remains relatively strong though we're watching it carefully. The markets have been robust, as you can see from our trading results.</p>
          <p>On rates, I think we need to be prepared for a wide range of outcomes. The Fed has a tough job balancing inflation concerns with economic growth. We're positioned for various scenarios, but I wouldn't want to predict exactly where rates will be. We manage the company to perform well across different environments.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="3" type="q">
        <plist>
          <p>Thanks. And as a follow-up, on capital, your CET1 ratio of 15% is well above your requirement. How are you thinking about capital deployment priorities going forward?</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="2" type="a">
        <plist>
          <p>Thanks for the question. We're very comfortable with our capital position. At 15%, we have about 60 basis points of buffer above our requirement. Our priorities remain consistent - first is organic growth to support our clients and businesses, second is the dividend which we view as a commitment, and third is buybacks.</p>
          <p>We'll continue to be opportunistic on buybacks. This quarter we bought back $3.3 billion, and we have capacity to continue at a healthy pace going forward while maintaining a prudent buffer.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <!-- Question 2 -->
      <speaker id="0">
        <plist>
          <p>Thank you. Our next question comes from Betsy Graseck with Morgan Stanley. Your line is open.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="4" type="q">
        <plist>
          <p>Hi, good morning. I wanted to ask about the net interest income outlook. You saw some compression in deposit margins this quarter. How should we think about the trajectory from here, particularly if the Fed does start cutting rates?</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="2" type="a">
        <plist>
          <p>Thanks, Betsy. On NII, we saw continued deposit margin compression this quarter as expected. The pace of migration to higher-yielding products is moderating but continuing.</p>
          <p>Looking forward, in a rate cut scenario, we would expect to see some relief on deposit costs over time, though there's typically a lag. Our asset yields would also reprice down, but we have a favorable mix with a good portion of floating rate assets.</p>
          <p>Overall, we're comfortable with our positioning. We've been preparing for various rate scenarios and believe we can manage through different environments effectively.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="4" type="q">
        <plist>
          <p>Great. And as a follow-up, can you talk about credit trends in the card portfolio? The charge-off rate increased year-over-year. Are you seeing any particular pockets of stress?</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="1" type="a">
        <plist>
          <p>The card portfolio is performing as we expected. Yes, charge-offs are up year-over-year, but they're normalizing from historically low levels. We're seeing some stress in lower income cohorts and younger borrowers, which is not surprising given the economic environment.</p>
          <p>But overall, the portfolio remains healthy. We've been tightening underwriting standards where appropriate and feel good about our reserve levels. This is all very manageable and within our expectations.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <!-- Additional Q&A pairs would continue here following the same pattern -->
      
      <!-- Final Question -->
      <speaker id="0">
        <plist>
          <p>Thank you. Our next question comes from Chris Kotowski with Oppenheimer. Your line is open.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="16" type="q">
        <plist>
          <p>Good morning. I wanted to ask about the investment banking pipeline. You had strong results this quarter. What are you seeing in terms of client activity and the forward calendar?</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="1" type="a">
        <plist>
          <p>The investment banking environment has improved considerably. We're seeing good dialogue with clients, healthy M&amp;A discussions, and a robust pipeline. The debt capital markets remain active, and we're starting to see more equity issuance as well.</p>
          <p>I think CEO confidence has improved, and that's translating into more strategic activity. The pipeline looks good, though as always, it depends on market conditions and various external factors. But overall, we're optimistic about the trajectory.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="16" type="q">
        <plist>
          <p>That's helpful. And just quickly on expenses, they were up 11% this quarter. How should we think about the expense trajectory for the rest of the year?</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="2" type="a">
        <plist>
          <p>On expenses, the increase this quarter was driven by higher revenue-related compensation in Markets and continued technology investments. For the full year, we still expect expenses to be in the range of $91 to $92 billion, excluding any significant legal costs.</p>
          <p>We continue to invest in technology and talent while maintaining discipline on efficiency. We'll manage expenses dynamically based on the revenue environment.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <!-- Closing -->
      <speaker id="0">
        <plist>
          <p>Thank you. And that concludes our question and answer session. I'll now turn the call back to Jamie Dimon for closing remarks.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="1">
        <plist>
          <p>Thank you all for joining us today. We're pleased with our strong performance this quarter and remain focused on serving our clients and communities. We're well-positioned for whatever lies ahead, and we'll continue to invest in our businesses for the long term.</p>
          <p>Thanks again, and we'll speak to you next quarter.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
      
      <speaker id="0">
        <plist>
          <p>Thank you, all, for participating in today's conference. You may disconnect at this time and have a great day.</p>
        </plist>
      </speaker>
    </section>
  </body>
</transcript>